Guide to the Yale Review Records: 1911-1949
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1907-1953; Series I; 5.46; (13 boxes)
  - Livingston, Richard, Sir, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Lodge, Oliver, Sir, 1918-1924 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas R., 1914-1916 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    With holographs, signed, of "Histriomastix" and "The Teutonic Invasion of England"
  - Lowell, Amy, 1915-1923 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    With typescript carbon of "Profession" and printed copy of "Trades"
  - Lowes, John Livingston, 1919-0 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - "Ma" to "Me" general, 1911-1946 (Box 8, Folder 250)
    Macauley, Rose
    MacIntyre, C.F.
    MacKaye, Percy
    Mackenzie, Compton
    MacMurray, J.V.A.
    MacNeice, Louis
    Mallon, Guy W.
    Malone, Dumas
    de Man, Henry, Dr.
    Marcham, Frederick G.
    Marcovitch, B.L.
    Marcus, Paul
    Marion, J.H.
    Maritain, Jacques
    Marquis, Don
    Marshall, S.L.A.
    Martin, Albert T.
    Martin, Charles
    Martin, Kingsley
    Mason, Daniel Gregory
    Mason, Lawrence
    Mayer, E.
    McCord, David
    McGovern, James L.
    McGuire, C.E.
    McLane, James
    Mears, Helen
    Mendenhall, Marjorie S.
    Merz, Charles
    Meyerfeld, Max, Dr.
  - "Mi" to "Mz" general, 1914-1947 (Box 8, Folder 251)
    Micaud, Charles A.
    Millikan, Robert A.
    Millington, C. Norris
    Mirsky, Prince D.S.
    Mitchell, Wesley C.
    Mitrany, David
    Moley, Raymond
    Moore, Douglas
    Moore, George
    Moore, Merrill
    Moore, Virginia
    Moos, Malcolm
    More, Paul E.
    Morgan, T.H.
    Morison, S.E.
    Morley, Frank V.
    Morse, John T.
    Munger, Elizabeth
    Murdock, Kenneth B.
  - Mackay, Anstruther, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1920-1945 (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - McFee, William, 1922-1942 (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - McLeod, Irene, 1916-1920 (Box 8, Folder 255)
    With holographs of "At Parting," "Discharged," "The Absent Lover," and "Missing"
  - Madariaga, Salvador de, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Manly, John Matthews, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Mann, Thomas, 1931-1945 (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - March, Peyton, General, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Marshall, Archibald, 1921-1922 (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Martin, Houston, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Masefield, John, 1913-1931 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    With typescript, signed, and galley proof, corrected, of "The Passing "Strange"
  - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1915-1924 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Matthews, Brander, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Matthiessen, F.O., 1931-1950 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Maurois, André, 1927-1942 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    With typescript, corrected, and galley proof, incomplete, of "The Modern Biography"
  - Mencken, H.L., 1932-1948 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1917-1923 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Millis, Walter, 1921-1945 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Montague, C.E., 1926-1928 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Morgan, Charles, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    With holograph, signed, and galley proof, corrected, of his review of "Panic"
  - Morley, Christopher, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Morewood, Margaret T., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    With transcripts and photograph of documents concerning Allan Melville
  - Morris, Edward P., 1915-1930 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Mosely, Philip, 1938-1946 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    With typescript, corrected, signed, of a letter on the state of the arts
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1921-1932 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Murry, J. Middleton, 1922-1924 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - "N" general, 1921-1946 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    Nash, Paul
    Nicolson, Marjorie H.
    Nixon, Glenn
    Nolan, J. Bennett
    Northrup, F.S.
    Notestein, Wallace, Mrs.
    Nourse, Edwin G., Dr.
    Noyes, Alexander D.
    Noyes, C. Reinold
  - Nichols, Robert, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Nicholson, Meredith, 1911-1924 (Box 8, Folder 282-283)
  - Nicolson, Harold, 1928-1935 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Noel-Baker, Philip, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Noyes, Alfred, 1913-1920 (Box 9, Folder 286)
    With holograph of "The Union"
  - "O" general, 1911-1943 (Box 9, Folder 287)
    Oberholtzer, Ellis P.
    Oberling, Charles, Dr.
    O'Brien, Kate
    O'Casey, Sean
    O'Connor, Frank
    Ofaire, Alette
    Olds, Leland
    Orth, Samuel P.
    Osborn, Henry Fairfield
    Osler, William, Sir
    Oviatt, Edwin
  - O'Faolain, Sean, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 288)
    With typescript, corrected, of "The Material of Irish Literature in the 1930s"
  - O'Neill, Eugene, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Oppegard, Roy W., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - "Pa-Peel" general, 1914-1943 (Box 9, Folder 291)
    Palmer, John M.
    Panunzio, Constantino
    Pardee, John S.
    Parr, A.E.
    Paterson, Isabel
    Pearl, Raymond
    Pears, Edwin, Sir
    Peattie, Donald Culross
    Peel, Albert
  - "Per-Pi" general, 1913-1945 (Box 9, Folder 292)
    Percy, William A.
    Perry, Ralph Barton
    Perry, Thomas S.
    Petersoe, Julius
    Petrunkevitch, Alexander
    Peyre, Henri
    Philip, Hoffman
    Phillips, Duncan
    Pier, Arthur S.
  - "Po-Pr" general, 1913-1936 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    Pollard, A.F.
    Ponafidene, Emma
    Porter, A. Kingsley
    Powell, Thomas Reed
    Power, Eileen
    Price, A. Grenfell
    Prindle, Frances C., Mrs.
  - Parker, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 294)
    Typescript, signed, of "Take My Vows"
  - Parker, Horatio, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Peabody, Francis, 1922-1925 (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Peffer, Nathaniel, 1936-1941 (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Perry, Bliss, 1912-1930 (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Petrie, W.M. Flinders, Sir, 1918-1926 (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1911-1940 (Box 9, Folder 300-301)
  - Plunkett, Horace, Sir, 1918-1920 (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Price, Lucien, 1930-1936 (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Pupin, Michael, 1927-1934 (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Putnam, H. Phelps, 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - "Q" general, 1923-1929 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    Quigley, Harold Scott
    Quinn, Arthur Hobson
  - "Ra-Ri" general, 1912-1944 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    Randall, J.G.
    Ratchford, Fannie
    Read, Herbert
    Redlich, Joseph
    Rhodes, James F.
    Ripley, William Z.
  - "Rob-Rom" general, 1917-1939 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    Robinson, James H.
    Rodman, Selden
    Rogers, James
    Rogers, Lindsay
    Rolland, Romain
    Romains, M. Jules
  - "Roo-Ru" general, 1914-1942 (Box 9, Folder 310)
    Root, E. Talmadge, Rev.
    Ross, Edward Alsworth
    Rostovtzeff, Michael
    Rourke, Constance
    Roy, Basanta Koomar
    Russell, Henry N.
    Rustomjee, Rustom
  - Raleigh, Walter Alexander, Sir, 1911-1915 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Ransom, John Crowe, 1915-1938 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    With typescript, corrected, of a page from "Sentimental Exercises"
  - Ratcliffe, S.K., 1929-1948 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Read, Conyers, 1933-1936 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Reinhardt, Max, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 315)
    Typescript, corrected, signed, of "Vom Schauspieler"
  - Repplier, Agnes, 1916-1935 (Box 9, Folder 316-317)
  - Reynaud, M. Paul, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Richards, I.A., 1931-1943 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Richards, Laura E., Mrs., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1913-1932 (Box 9, Folder 321-322)
    With typescript corrected, signed, of "Nicodemus," 1930.
  - Root, Elihu, 1911-1931 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Roselli, Bruno, 1920-1929 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    With signed offprint of "Un italiano donatore di regni all'America," 1929
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Rowell, Chester H., 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Royce, Josiah and Katharine, 1915-1931 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Russell, George ("AE"), 1926-1928 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    With typescript, signed, of "Three Poems"
  - Rutherford, Ernest, Sir, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - "Sa-Si" general, 1911-1946 (Box 10, Folder 331)
    Sadler, Michael
    Salisbury, Laurence
    Salvemini, Gaetano
    Sarton, May
    Schacht, Hjalmar
    Sedgwick, G.S.
    Sedgwick, H.D.
    Sedgwick, W.T.
    Seymour, Charles
    Seymour, George D.
    Sforza, Carlo, Count
    Shaplen, Elaine
    Sherman, Jame
    Sherman, M.S.
    Shoemaker, James H.
    Shorey, Paul
    Showerman, Grant
    Sidersky, Olga
    Sigerist, Henry E., Dr.
    Simonds, Bruce
    Simpson, Hartley
    Singer, Kurt
    Sinnott, Edmund W.
  - "Sk-So" general, 1913-1946 (Box 10, Folder 332)
    Skinner, Constance Lindsay
    Slonim, Marc, Dr.
    Smith, David Stanley
    Smith, Justin H.
    Smith, Roy C.
    Smith, T.V.
    Smythe, Daniel
    Snowden, Philip, Viscount
    Snyder, Carl
    Snyder, Howard
    Sokol, A.E.
    Sorokine, Pitriam A.
  - "Sp-Stie" general, 1914-1946 (Box 10, Folder 333)
    Spencer, J.W.
    Speranza, Gino
    Sperry, Willard L.
    Spingarn, J.E.
    Sprague, O.M.W.
    Stark, Louis
    Staudinger, Hans, Dr.
    Stauffer, Donald A., Captain
    Steiner, Herbert, Dr.
    Sternberg, Fritz
    Stewart, George R.
    Stieglitz, Julius
  - "Sti-Sy" general, 1914-1940 (Box 10, Folder 334)
    Still, James
    Stonehill, Charles A.
    Stonehill, H. Winthrop
    Stoper, Gustav, Dr.
    Storm, Hans Otto
    Strong, L.A.G.
    Strong, Richard P.
    Strunsky, Simeon
    Stuart, E.R., Lieut.
    Sullivan, Richard
    Suyemoto, Toyo
    Swing, Raymond Gram
    Swinnerton, Frank
    Synge, E.H.
  - Santayana, George, 1923-1928 (Box 10, Folder 335)
    With holograph, signed, of "A Preface to a System of Philosophy"
  - Saroyan, William, 1935-1939 (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Sackville-West, Vita, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 337)
    With typescript of "Thirty Clocks Strike the Hour"
  - Salter, Arthur, 1924-1939 (Box 10, Folder 338)
    Typescript, corrected, of "The Perils of Recovery"
  - Sasson, Siegfried, 1918-1921 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Schorer, Mark, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1919-1946 (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - Sheldon, Charles, 1911-1920 (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Sherman, Stuart P., 1911-1924 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Siegfried, Andre, 1929-1935 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Simonson, Lee, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Sinclair, May, 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Slichter, Sumner H., 1922-1946 (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1932 (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Smuts, Jan Christiaan, General, 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Spender, J.A., 1927-1934 (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Stallings, Laurence, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Steed, Wickham, 1926-1931 (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1921-1933 (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Steffens, Lincoln, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Stein, Gertrude, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - Stein, Gunther, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - Sterling, George, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 358)
    Typescript, signed, of "To Pain"
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1912-1948 (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1911-1928 (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - Strachey, Lytton, 1918-1922 (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Stuart, Jesse, 1933-1938 (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Sumner, William Graham, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    Holograph of "Earth Hunger"
  - Symons, Arthur, 1916-1918 (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - "Ta-Th" general, 1912-1946 (Box 11, Folder 367)
    Talbot, Melvin F.
    Tardrey
    Taylor, Deems
    Taylor, Henry Osborn
    Thayer, William R.
    Thielen, Benedict
    Thomas, T.H., Major
    Thompson, Wallace Fawcett
    Thurnwald, Richard C.
  - "Ti-Ty" general, 1911-1946 (Box 11, Folder 368)
    Tillotson, Geoffrey
    Tinayre, Marcelle, Mme.
    Tinker, Edward Larocque
    Tolstoy, Alexandra
    Torrence, Olivia H.D., Mrs.
    Torrence, Ridgely
    Torrey, Charles C.
    Treat, Ida,
    Trevelyan, G.M.
    Tsao, Yun-hsiang
    Tsurumi, Yusuke
    Tunney, Gene
    Turner, Raymond
    Tyler, Dorothy
  - Taft, William Howard, 1911-1928 (Box 11, Folder 369-370)
  - Taggard, Genevieve, 1939-1950 (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Tarbell, Ida M., 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 372)
    With holograph, signed, of review of Lincoln biographies
  - Tate, Allen, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 373)
    With typescript of "The End: To Archibald MacLeish"
  - Taussig, F.W., 1933-1940 (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Teasdale, Sara, 1916-1926 (Box 11, Folder 375-376)
    With typescript, signed, of "August Night"
  - Thayer, William Roscoe, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 377)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1918-1946 (Box 11, Folder 378)
  - Tomlinson, H.M., 1923-1940 (Box 11, Folder 379)
    With typescript of "War Books"
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1933-1939 (Box 11, Folder 380)
  - Trotsky, Leon
    Related Archival Materials note
    See: Charles Rumford Walker, Box 12, folder 393
  - Turner, Frederick J., 1922-1927 (Box 11, Folder 381)
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1915-1946 (Box 11, Folder 382-383)
  - "V" general, 1912-1944 (Box 11, Folder 384)
    Van Doren, Mark
    Vaill, Dudley L.
    VanSantvoord, George
    Van Slyke, Beren
    Van Tyne, Claude Halstead
    Vernadsky, George
    Verplanck, William
    Vesnitch, Milenko R.
    Villari, Luigi
    Vincenti, George E.
    Viner, Jacob
    Vinogradoff, Paul, Sir
    Vogt, William
    Von der Leyen, F.
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1911-1930 (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - Valéry, Paul, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 386)
    Typescript, signed, of "Reflexions"
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem, 1918-1921 (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - "Wa" general, 1912-1946 (Box 11, Folder 388)
    Walker, Hugh
    Walker, Williston
    Walkley, A.B.
    Wallas, Graham
    Wambaugh, Eugene
    Wang, Chenting T.
    Warren, Charles
    Washington, George Thomas
    Watkins, Myron Webster
    Wattles, Willard
    Watts, Richard
  - "We-Wes" general, 1924-1942 (Box 11, Folder 389)
    Wechsberg, Joseph
    Wei, Francis C.M.
    Weismiller, Edward
    Wellard, James H.
    Welles, Halsted
    Welles, Sumner
    Wells-Houghton, Carolyn
    Welty, Eudora
    Wescott, Eugene M.
    West, Geoffrey
    Westbrook, H. Theodric
    Westermann, W.L.
  - "Wh" general, 1911-1945 (Box 11, Folder 390)
    Wharton, J.G.
    Wheeler, W. Reginald
    Wheeler-Bennett, John W.
    Whicher, George F.
    Whipple. T.K.
    White, Andrew D.
    White, E.B.
    White, Leonard D.
    White, Paul Lambert
    Whiting Arthur
    Whitlock, Brand
    Whitney, Simon N.
  - "Wic-Wil" general, 1913-1945 (Box 11, Folder 391)
    Wickersham, George W.
    Wilhelm, Gale, Mrs.
    Willcox, William
    Williams, Albert R.
    Williams, L.F. Rushbrook
    Williams, W.M.J.
    Wilson, E.B.
    Wilson, George G.
    Wilson, Margaret Woodrow
    Winslow, Anne Goodwin, Mrs.
    Winston, Garrard
  - "Wo" general, 1914-1917 (Box 11, Folder 392)
    Wolfe, Humbert
    Wolfers, Arnold
    Wolman, Leo
    Wood, Clement
    Woodward, E.L.
    Woollcott, Alexander
  - Walker, Charles Rumford, 1933-1938 (Box 12, Folder 393)
  - Walpole, Hugh, Sir, 1920-1933 (Box 12, Folder 394)
    With typescript, corrected, of untitled article
  - Warner, Edward P., 1920-1940 (Box 12, Folder 395)
  - Wecter, Dixon, 1940-1946 (Box 12, Folder 396)
  - Wells, H.G., 1917-1921 (Box 12, Folder 397)
    With page proof, corrected, of "History for Everybody"
  - Wendell, Barrett, 1916-1918 (Box 12, Folder 398)
  - West, Rebecca, 1919-1933 (Box 12, Folder 399)
    With holograph, signed, of a review of several novels
  - Wharton, Edith, 1912-1930 (Box 12, Folder 400-401)
    With page of typescript, signed, of "The Great American Novel"
  - Wheelock, John Hall, 1922-1932 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - White, William Allen, 1916-1943 (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - White, Thomas Raeburn, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - White, William L., 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1915-1918 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Willkie, Wendell L., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1928-1940 (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1915-1919 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Wister, Owen D., 1921 (Box 13, Folder 410)
    With holograph, signed, of "The Master Builder"
  - Wolfe, Thomas, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 411)
  - Woolf, Virginia, 1926-39, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 412-19)
    With typescripts, corrected, of
    "The Art of Walter Sickert", "Street
    Haunting," "Augustine Birrell," "The
    Novels of Turgenev," and "Letter to
    a Young Poet;" typescript, corrected
    and signed, of "How Should One Read
    a Book?;" and galley proofs, corrected,
    of "The Novels of Turgenev" and
    "Augustine Birrell."
  - Woodberry, George E., 1911 (Box 13, Folder 420)
  - Wroth, Lawrence C., 1927 (Box 13, Folder 421)
  - Wylie, Elinor, 1921-1927 (Box 13, Folder 422)
  - "Y" general, 1928-1942 (Box 13, Folder 423)
    Yale, William
    Yang, F.Y.
    Yen, T.C. James
  - Young, Francis Brett, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 424)
  - Young, George, Sir, 1925-1930 (Box 13, Folder 425)
    With holograph of "The East Goes West"
  - Young, Owen D., 1925-1942 (Box 13, Folder 426)
  - Young, Stark, 1918-1926 (Box 13, Folder 427)
  - Zimmern, Alfred, 1919-1928 (Box 13, Folder 428)
  - Zangwill, Israel, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 429)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 14 (Box 14, Folder 430)
  - Box 1, folder 15 (Box 14, Folder 431)
  - Box 1, folder 20 (Box 14, Folder 432)
  - Box 1, folder 29 (Box 14, Folder 433)
  - Box 1, folder 30 (Box 14, Folder 434)
  - Box 1, folder 31 (Box 14, Folder 435)
  - Box 1, folder 42 (Box 14, Folder 436)
  - Box 2, folder 46 (Box 14, Folder 437)
  - Box 2, folder 48 (Box 14, Folder 438)
  - Box 2, folder 55 (Box 14, Folder 439)
  - Box 2, folder 61 (Box 14, Folder 440)
  - Box 2, folder 70 (Box 14, Folder 441)
  - Box 2, folder 73 (Box 14, Folder 442)
  - Box 2, folder 74 (Box 14, Folder 443)
  - Box 2, folder 75 (Box 14, Folder 444)
  - Box 2, folder 79 (Box 14, Folder 445)
  - Box 2, folder 86 (Box 14, Folder 446)
  - Box 3, folder 93 (Box 14, Folder 447)
  - Box 3, folder 103 (Box 14, Folder 448)
  - Box 3, folder 104 (Box 14, Folder 449)
  - Box 3, folder 109 (Box 14, Folder 450)
  - Box 3, folder 110 (Box 14, Folder 451)
  - Box 3, folder 115 (Box 14, Folder 452)
  - Box 4, folder 118 (Box 14, Folder 453)
  - Box 4, folder 123 (Box 14, Folder 454)
  - Box 4, folder 126 (Box 14, Folder 455)
  - Box 4, folder 128 (Box 14, Folder 456)
  - Box 4, folder 130 (Box 14, Folder 457)
  - Box 4, folder 135 (Box 14, Folder 458)
  - Box 4, folder 138 (Box 14, Folder 459)
  - Box 4, folder 144 (Box 14, Folder 460)
  - Box 4, folder 147 (Box 14, Folder 461)
  - Box 4, folder 148 (Box 14, Folder 462)
  - Box 5, folder 155 (Box 14, Folder 463)
  - Box 5, folder 167 (Box 14, Folder 464)
  - Box 5, folder 169 (Box 14, Folder 465)
  - Box 5, folder 170 (Box 14, Folder 466)
  - Box 5, folder 171 (Box 14, Folder 467)
  - Box 5, folder 173 (Box 14, Folder 468)
  - Box 5, folder 176 (Box 14, Folder 469)
  - Box 5, folder 177 (Box 14, Folder 470)
  - Box 5, folder 179 (Box 14, Folder 471)
  - Box 6, folder 188 (Box 14, Folder 472)
  - Box 6, folder 211 (Box 14, Folder 473)
  - Box 6, folder 218 (Box 14, Folder 474)
  - Box 6, folder 219 (Box 14, Folder 475)
  - Box 7, folder 220 (Box 14, Folder 476)
  - Box 7, folder 235 (Box 14, Folder 477)
  - Box 7, folder 241 (Box 14, Folder 478)
  - Box 7, folder 244 (Box 14, Folder 479)
  - Box 8, folder 280 (Box 14, Folder 480)
  - Box 9, folder 286 (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Box 9, folder 287 (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Box 9, folder 290 (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Box 9, folder 291 (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Box 9, folder 292 (Box 14, Folder 485)
  - Box 9, folder 300 (Box 14, Folder 486)
  - Box 9, folder 308 (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - Box 9, folder 312 (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - Box 9, folder 313 (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - Box 9, folder 316 (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - Box 9, folder 327 (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - Box 9, folder 329 (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - Box 10, folder 331 (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - Box 10, folder 331 (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Box 10, folder 333 (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Box 10, folder 334 (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - Box 10, folder 335 (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - Box 10, folder 337 (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - Box 10, folder 344 (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - Box 10, folder 348 (Box 14, Folder 500)
  - Box 10, folder 349 (Box 14, Folder 501)
  - Box 10, folder 351 (Box 14, Folder 502)
  - Box 10, folder 354 (Box 14, Folder 503)
  - Box 10, folder 361 (Box 14, Folder 504)
  - Box 10, folder 365 (Box 14, Folder 505)
  - Box 11, folder 367 (Box 14, Folder 506)
  - Box 11, folder 369 (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Box 11, folder 375 (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Box 11, folder 382 (Box 14, Folder 509)
  - Box 11, folder 387 (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - Box 11, folder 392 (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Box 12, folder 393 (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Box 12, folder 397 (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Box 12, folder 399 (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Box 12, folder 400 (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Box 12, folder 401 (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Box 12, folder 403 (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Box 12, folder 404 (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Box 12, folder 409 (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Box 13, folder 414 (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Box 13, folder 425 (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Box 13, folder 429 (Box 14, Folder 522)